<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Financial Planning on ExcelNav</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/financial-planning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Financial Planning on ExcelNav</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/financial-planning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Balloon Loan Payment Calculator: Plan Installments &amp; Final Lump-Sum Payments Effortlessly</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/balance-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/balance-sheet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-detailed-description&#34;&gt;1. Detailed Description​&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The ​Balloon Loan Payment Calculator​ is a specialized financial tool designed for loans with lower monthly payments and a large &amp;ldquo;balloon&amp;rdquo; payment due at the end of the term. Ideal for auto loans, commercial mortgages, or short-term financing, this calculator helps users:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Estimate ​monthly payments​ during the loan term.&#xA;Calculate the ​total interest cost​ and ​final balloon payment.&#xA;Compare scenarios by adjusting loan amounts, interest rates, and terms.&#xA;By inputting the principal, annual interest rate, amortization period, and balloon term, users gain transparency into their repayment obligations, ensuring informed financial decisions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annuity investment calculator</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/annuity-investment-calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/annuity-investment-calculator/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;annuity-investment-calculator--excel-template&#34;&gt;Annuity Investment Calculator – Excel Template&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1detailed-description&#34;&gt;（1）Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Annuity Investment Calculator is a powerful Excel-based tool designed to simulate and track the growth of an annuity investment over time. Users can input the initial present value, annual interest rate, investment term, and monthly reinvestment rate to automatically calculate monthly interest earned, payout amounts, and updated balances. The template supports up to 20 years (240 months) of detailed monthly analysis and highlights key milestones such as the 7-year, 10-year, 14-year, and 20-year marks. Ideal for individual investors, financial advisors, and educational purposes, this tool helps visualize compound interest and long-term investment returns effectively.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
