<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Education Planning on ExcelNav</title>
    <link>https://excelnav.com/tags/education-planning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Education Planning on ExcelNav</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://excelnav.com/tags/education-planning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Academic calendar</title>
      <link>https://excelnav.com/templates/academic-calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://excelnav.com/templates/academic-calendar/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;academic-calendar-excel-template-organize-your-school-year-efficiently&#34;&gt;Academic Calendar Excel Template: Organize Your School Year Efficiently&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;detailed-description&#34;&gt;Detailed Description&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Academic Calendar Template is a versatile and user-friendly Excel-based tool designed to help schools, teachers, students, and parents plan and track academic activities throughout the school year. It covers a full 12-month period from September 2025 to August 2026, with each week clearly laid out from Monday to Sunday. The template uses automated formulas to generate dates and weekdays, minimizing manual input and ensuring accuracy. It’s ideal for marking important events such as parent-teacher conferences, exams, holidays, and project deadlines. Whether you’re managing a school schedule or organizing personal study plans, this template offers a structured and reusable format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academic calendar with photos</title>
      <link>https://excelnav.com/templates/academic-calendar-with-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://excelnav.com/templates/academic-calendar-with-photos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;file-structure&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;File Structure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1detailed-description&#34;&gt;（1）Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This “Academic Calendar with Photos” Excel template is a visually engaging and highly functional educational planning tool designed for students, teachers, school administrators, and homeschooling parents. It spans a full academic year from September 2025 to August 2026, organized by weeks and months with automatic day and date generation. The template includes dedicated note sections for key events such as parent-teacher conferences, exams, and holidays. Its clean layout supports photo insertion for personalization, making it ideal for academic scheduling, project tracking, and visual planning. Whether used in classrooms or at home, this template helps users manage their academic year efficiently and creatively.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
