<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Free Excel Templates Download - Professional Spreadsheet Collection | ExcelNav on ExcelNav</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Free Excel Templates Download - Professional Spreadsheet Collection | ExcelNav on ExcelNav</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/templates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>《Ultimate Assignment Tracker: Course Management &#43; Dynamic Filters &#43; Progress Visualization》</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/assignment-schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/assignment-schedule/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;excel-template--documentation&#34;&gt;Excel Template – Documentation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-detailed-description&#34;&gt;(1) ​Detailed Description​&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;《Assignment Schedule.xlsx》is an education-focused task tracking spreadsheet designed for students, instructors, or training coordinators. It features visual progress bars, course filters, and date sorting to manage multi-course assignments efficiently. The PivotTable supports dynamic refresh, while slicers enable quick filtering by course (e.g., Basic Life Support), instructor, progress percentage (0%-100%), or due date (e.g., due in 2 days). Ideal for monitoring strict deadlines in medical training (e.g., EMT, Anatomy).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby Growth Tracker: Monitor Your Infant&#39;s Development</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/baby-growth-chart/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/baby-growth-chart/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;excel-template--documentation&#34;&gt;Excel Template – Documentation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;detailed-description&#34;&gt;Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This comprehensive baby growth chart template helps parents meticulously track their infant&amp;rsquo;s physical development during the crucial early years. The spreadsheet records weight (in pounds and ounces), length measurements, and corresponding percentile rankings according to standard pediatric growth charts. Designed for newborns up to 36 months, it captures key milestones from birth through toddlerhood with precision. Pediatricians recommend regular monitoring of these metrics to ensure healthy development patterns. The color-coded percentile columns instantly visualize whether your child is following typical growth curves compared to population averages. Perfect for well-baby visits, this tool transforms raw measurements into actionable insights about your little one&amp;rsquo;s health.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to School Planner: Smart Budget &#43; Task Tracker Excel Template for Parents</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/back-to-school-planner/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/back-to-school-planner/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;back-to-school-planner-the-comprehensive-guide-for-parents--student-preparation-master-list&#34;&gt;Back to School Planner: The Comprehensive Guide for Parents | Student Preparation Master List&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-detailed-description&#34;&gt;(1). Detailed Description&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Back to School Planner is a versatile Excel tool designed for parents and students to streamline pre-semester preparations. This integrated spreadsheet combines budget tracking, shopping lists, to-do tasks, and collaboration features, enabling users to allocate education expenses (e.g., textbooks, uniforms, supplies) efficiently. With real-time budget summaries and progress bars, users can monitor spending and prevent overspending. The one-click sharing functionality facilitates family collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balloon Loan Payment Calculator: Plan Installments &amp; Final Lump-Sum Payments Effortlessly</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/balance-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/balance-sheet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-detailed-description&#34;&gt;1. Detailed Description​&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The ​Balloon Loan Payment Calculator​ is a specialized financial tool designed for loans with lower monthly payments and a large &amp;ldquo;balloon&amp;rdquo; payment due at the end of the term. Ideal for auto loans, commercial mortgages, or short-term financing, this calculator helps users:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Estimate ​monthly payments​ during the loan term.&#xA;Calculate the ​total interest cost​ and ​final balloon payment.&#xA;Compare scenarios by adjusting loan amounts, interest rates, and terms.&#xA;By inputting the principal, annual interest rate, amortization period, and balloon term, users gain transparency into their repayment obligations, ensuring informed financial decisions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom Yearly Calendar Template: Printable Excel Calendar for 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/any-year-custom-calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/any-year-custom-calendar/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;excel-template--documentation&#34;&gt;Excel Template – Documentation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-detailed-description&#34;&gt;(1). ​Detailed Description​&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Any Year Custom Calendar is a flexible Excel template that enables users to generate personalized calendars by customizing the year, start day, and theme styles. It supports printing or exporting as PDF, ideal for home, school, or office use. The template auto-adjusts date layouts, includes monthly labels and notes sections, helping users efficiently schedule events and track important dates.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-use-cases&#34;&gt;(2). ​Use Cases​&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;​Family Planning: Track birthdays, holidays, and family events.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free 2025 Printable Excel Calendar Template | Editable &amp; Downloadable</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/any-year-calendar-ion-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/any-year-calendar-ion-theme/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;excel-template--documentation&#34;&gt;Excel Template – Documentation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-detailed-description&#34;&gt;1. Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 2025 Full-Year Calendar Template is a customizable tool designed for individuals and teams, featuring complete monthly layouts from January to December 2025. With a clean Sunday-to-Saturday weekly view and unique date serials (e.g., 45655 for Jan 1, 2025), it includes dedicated &amp;ldquo;NOTES&amp;rdquo; sections for reminders. Ideal for daily planning or project tracking, this Excel-compatible file supports easy edits.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-use-cases&#34;&gt;2. Use Cases&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;​Personal Scheduling: Mark birthdays, anniversaries, or daily tasks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Baby Growth Chart Template: Track Weight &amp; Height Percentiles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/baby-growth-tracker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/baby-growth-tracker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;baby-growth-tracker-the-ultimate-tool-for-monitoring-your-infants-development&#34;&gt;Baby Growth Tracker: The Ultimate Tool for Monitoring Your Infant&amp;rsquo;s Development&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;detailed-description&#34;&gt;Detailed Description&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Baby Growth Tracker is a comprehensive Excel spreadsheet designed to help parents and caregivers meticulously record and visualize their infant&amp;rsquo;s growth metrics. This tool automatically tracks weight (in pounds/ounces), length (in inches), and percentile rankings from birth through 36 months. With built-in growth charts, it transforms raw data into easy-to-understand visual progress reports, eliminating the guesswork from developmental monitoring. Pediatricians recommend regular growth tracking to ensure healthy development, and this template provides hospital-grade accuracy for home use.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Balance Sheet Template - Track Assets &amp; Liabilities with Auto Calculations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/balance-sheet-simple/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/balance-sheet-simple/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-detailed-description&#34;&gt;1. Detailed Description&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This Balance Sheet Template is a powerful tool designed to help businesses and individuals track their financial health by automatically calculating total assets, liabilities, and owner&amp;rsquo;s equity. The template features organized sections for current/fixed/other assets, current/long-term liabilities, and equity investments. Formulas are pre-built to sum categories and validate the accounting equation (Assets = Liabilities + Owner&amp;rsquo;s Equity). A year-over-year comparison chart provides visual trend analysis, making it ideal for financial reporting, investor presentations, or loan applications. The template includes cell tips with instructions and supports accessibility features like alternative text for tables.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professional Business Invoice Template Excel - Free Download for Small Businesses</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/basic-business-invoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/basic-business-invoice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;basic-business-invoice-template---streamline-your-billing-process&#34;&gt;Basic Business Invoice Template - Streamline Your Billing Process&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;detailed-description&#34;&gt;Detailed Description&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This professional invoice template is designed to help small businesses and freelancers create clear, standardized billing documents. The template includes all essential elements: company information, client details, itemized product/service descriptions, subtotal calculations, tax rate application, additional costs, and final total. With a clean layout and logical structure, it ensures your invoices look polished while making payment processing effortless for your clients. The template comes in Excel format for easy customization while maintaining a professional appearance that builds trust with your customers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streamline Client Management: Customizable Business Contact List Template with Geographic Analytics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/basic-customer-contact-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/basic-customer-contact-list/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-detailed-description&#34;&gt;(1) Detailed Description&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Basic Customer Contact List is a structured Excel template designed for SME customer relationship management. It systematically records customer ID, company name, detailed contact information (including name, title, communication channels) and geographic data (address, city, ZIP code, etc.). With standardized field formats, it seamlessly integrates with mainstream CRM systems to help users efficiently maintain client networks, optimize communication workflows, and analyze regional business distribution. Ideal for teams requiring regular customer follow-ups, regional marketing, or sales management.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Baby Shower Planner Excel Template: Guest Lists, Budget &amp; Task Tracker</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/baby-shower-planner/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/baby-shower-planner/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;baby-shower-planner-template-organize-the-perfect-celebration-effortlessly&#34;&gt;Baby Shower Planner Template: Organize the Perfect Celebration Effortlessly&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;detailed-description&#34;&gt;Detailed Description&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This Baby Shower Planner Excel template is designed to streamline every aspect of your baby shower event planning. It includes dedicated sections for guest management (tracking RSVPs, addresses, and party size), budget tracking (food/drinks, decorations, supplies), and task scheduling with time-sensitive reminders. The template features pre-formatted tables with auto-calculated totals, hidden instructional notes for guidance, and a clean layout for easy data entry. Ideal for hosts who want to avoid oversights, it ensures no detail is missed—from sending invitations to the final walkthrough before guests arrive.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Baby Shower Planner Excel Template: Guest Lists, Budget &amp; Task Tracker</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/basic-balance-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/basic-balance-sheet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-detailed-description&#34;&gt;（1）. ​Detailed Description​&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This Basic Balance Sheet Template is designed for Lamna Healthcare Company, providing a clear comparison of financial positions between 2024 and 2025. It includes three sections: ​Assets​ (current/fixed/other), ​Liabilities &amp;amp; Owner’s Equity​ (current/long-term/equity), and a yearly summary. Key metrics like cash, accounts receivable, investments, and payables are covered, ideal for analyzing liquidity, debt structure, and profitability. The template’s clean layout supports direct data input and instant calculations, making it a practical tool for accountants and entrepreneurs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Back-to-School Checklist: 23 Must-Do Tasks &#43; Printable</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/back-to-school-checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/back-to-school-checklist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;back-to-school-checklist-the-comprehensive-guide-for-parents--student-preparation-master-list&#34;&gt;Back to School Checklist: The Comprehensive Guide for Parents | Student Preparation Master List&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-detailed-description&#34;&gt;1. Detailed Description&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This back-to-school checklist is the ultimate organizational tool covering 8 critical categories across 23 core tasks. Designed with smart &amp;ldquo;TO DO/TO BUY/DONE&amp;rdquo; tracking columns, it systematically manages registration paperwork, medical exams, wardrobe preparation, school supplies procurement, and transportation arrangements. Special modules include safety training (memorizing emergency contacts, practicing commute routes) and routine establishment (bedtime schedules, homework stations), ensuring both logistical and psychological readiness for the new academic year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12-Month calendar</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/12-month-calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/12-month-calendar/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;file-structure&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;File Structure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1detailed-description&#34;&gt;（1）Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a powerful and highly customizable 12-month calendar Excel template designed for personal, family, or team use. It includes 12 sheets—one for each month—with automatic weekday display and support for custom year and week start (Monday or Sunday). The clean layout features dedicated spaces for events, making it easy to track birthdays, meetings, holidays, and more. Ideal for daily time management, family planning, or team coordination, this template helps you stay organized and productive throughout the year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academic calendar</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/academic-calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/academic-calendar/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;academic-calendar-excel-template-organize-your-school-year-efficiently&#34;&gt;Academic Calendar Excel Template: Organize Your School Year Efficiently&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;detailed-description&#34;&gt;Detailed Description&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Academic Calendar Template is a versatile and user-friendly Excel-based tool designed to help schools, teachers, students, and parents plan and track academic activities throughout the school year. It covers a full 12-month period from September 2025 to August 2026, with each week clearly laid out from Monday to Sunday. The template uses automated formulas to generate dates and weekdays, minimizing manual input and ensuring accuracy. It’s ideal for marking important events such as parent-teacher conferences, exams, holidays, and project deadlines. Whether you’re managing a school schedule or organizing personal study plans, this template offers a structured and reusable format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academic club budget</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/academic-club-budget/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/academic-club-budget/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;file-structure&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;File Structure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1detailed-description&#34;&gt;（1）Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Academic Club Budget is a financial management tool designed specifically for school academic clubs to track annual income and expenses effectively. It includes revenue sources such as membership dues, fundraisers, and donations, as well as common expenses like flyer printing and decorations. The sheet automatically calculates the budget for trips and the remaining amount needed, providing a clear overview of the club&amp;rsquo;s financial status. Ideal for middle schools, high schools, and universities, this template promotes financial transparency and efficient budget management for student-led organizations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activity costs tracker</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/activity-costs-tracker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/activity-costs-tracker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;activity-costs-tracker--excel-template&#34;&gt;Activity Costs Tracker – Excel Template&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-detailed-description&#34;&gt;(1) Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Activity Costs Tracker is an Excel-based cost management tool designed for small and medium-sized businesses that need to accurately track cost structures across multiple product lines. Based on the Activity-Based Costing (ABC) methodology, this template categorizes expenses into direct costs, indirect costs, and general &amp;amp; administrative costs. It automatically calculates the cost per unit and total weekly production costs for each product. With a clear structure and pre-built formulas, users can generate detailed cost summaries effortlessly, enabling better financial control and informed decision-making. Ideal for managers, accountants, and business owners seeking a practical and efficient way to monitor product profitability.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activity tracker</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/activity-tracker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/activity-tracker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;activity-tracker-spreadsheet--efficiently-log-your-fitness--health-data&#34;&gt;Activity Tracker Spreadsheet – Efficiently Log Your Fitness &amp;amp; Health Data&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-detailed-description&#34;&gt;(1) Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This &amp;ldquo;Activity Tracker&amp;rdquo; Excel spreadsheet is a practical tool designed for fitness enthusiasts to easily record and analyze their daily exercise data. It supports up to five customizable activities (such as biking, swimming, running, etc.) and automatically calculates the total amount of exercise (e.g., miles, steps, reps) and calories burned for each activity. Using built-in SUMIF and VLOOKUP functions, the sheet automatically summarizes data across different activities and links unit information to ensure consistency and readability. Users simply need to input the date, duration, total amount, and notes for each activity, and the sheet will generate categorized summaries and total calorie consumption—ideal for anyone committed to long-term fitness tracking.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Address and phone list</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/address-and-phone-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/address-and-phone-list/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;address-and-phone-list-template-introduction&#34;&gt;Address and Phone List Template Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1detailed-description&#34;&gt;（1）Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &amp;ldquo;Address and Phone List&amp;rdquo; is a practical template designed for managing personal or household contact information. It includes fields for last name, first name, family members, address, home number, work number, cell number, email, and contact type. This template helps users quickly access and organize important contacts such as friends, family, and colleagues. With a clean layout and support for real-time updates, it is ideal for maintaining a well-structured contact database. Whether used as a family address book, a team directory, or a personal network tracker, this template enhances communication efficiency and ensures your contacts are always up-to-date.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agile Gantt chart</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/agile-gantt-chart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/agile-gantt-chart/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;agile-gantt-chart-excel-template--documentation&#34;&gt;Agile Gantt Chart Excel Template – Documentation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-detailed-description&#34;&gt;1. Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Agile Gantt Chart Excel Template is a visual project management tool designed for agile teams and individuals to plan, track, and manage project timelines efficiently. It allows users to input tasks, set milestones, assign risk levels, and automatically generate a dynamic Gantt chart. By simply entering task details such as start date, duration, and progress percentage, users can visualize project flow and monitor deadlines with ease. Ideal for small to medium-sized projects, it supports flexible adjustments and clear progress tracking in an agile environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allowance tracker</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/allowance-tracker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/allowance-tracker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;allowance-tracker-excel-template--documentation&#34;&gt;Allowance tracker Excel Template – Documentation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1detailed-description&#34;&gt;（1）Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Robin&amp;rsquo;s Allowance Tracker is an Excel spreadsheet designed for families to systematically manage children&amp;rsquo;s chore completion and allowance earnings. It features multiple color-coded sheets (e.g., Blue, Green, Orange), each clearly listing tasks (e.g., Make Bed, Pickup Toys, Clean Room), their values, daily completion checks for each day of the week, and automatically calculated total earnings. With an intuitive checkmark system and automated summaries, parents can easily track children&amp;rsquo;s progress, fostering responsibility and financial literacy. Ideal for long-term use, the template supports multiple children or weeks, making it a practical tool for family management.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annuity investment calculator</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/annuity-investment-calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/annuity-investment-calculator/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;annuity-investment-calculator--excel-template&#34;&gt;Annuity Investment Calculator – Excel Template&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1detailed-description&#34;&gt;（1）Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Annuity Investment Calculator is a powerful Excel-based tool designed to simulate and track the growth of an annuity investment over time. Users can input the initial present value, annual interest rate, investment term, and monthly reinvestment rate to automatically calculate monthly interest earned, payout amounts, and updated balances. The template supports up to 20 years (240 months) of detailed monthly analysis and highlights key milestones such as the 7-year, 10-year, 14-year, and 20-year marks. Ideal for individual investors, financial advisors, and educational purposes, this tool helps visualize compound interest and long-term investment returns effectively.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Any year at a glance calendar landscape</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/any-year-at-a-glance-calendar-landscape/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/any-year-at-a-glance-calendar-landscape/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;any-year-at-a-glance-calendar-landscape--excel-template&#34;&gt;Any year at a glance calendar landscape – Excel Template&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1detailed-description&#34;&gt;（1）Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Any year at a glance calendar landscape.xlsx is a powerful and visually clear Excel template designed for yearly planning and tracking. Featuring a landscape layout, it automatically generates a full-year calendar based on user-defined year and start day of the week. Ideal for personal, family, or team use, this template helps users visualize entire years, track important dates, and plan ahead efficiently. Each month is displayed in a separate block with continuous date flow across months. Perfect for both digital and print use, it enhances productivity and time management.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free 2025 Printable Yearly Calendar Template</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/any-year-at-a-glance-calendar-portrait/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/any-year-at-a-glance-calendar-portrait/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;free-2025-printable-yearly-calendar-template&#34;&gt;Free 2025 Printable Yearly Calendar Template&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1detailed-description&#34;&gt;（1）Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This 2025 Year-at-a-Glance Calendar Excel sheet offers a clean portrait layout, displaying all months with dates arranged from Sunday to Saturday. Each date includes a serial number (e.g., 45658) for technical reference, making it suitable for printing or digital planning. Ideal for personal scheduling, project tracking, or family event management, this template ensures you stay organized and never miss a deadline.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;2use-cases&#34;&gt;（2）Use Cases&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Personal Planning: Track birthdays, vacations, or fitness goals.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Adjustable Meeting Agenda Template Excel - Professional Business Meeting Planner</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/adjustable-meeting-agenda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/adjustable-meeting-agenda/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;-adjustable-meeting-agendaxlsx--documentation&#34;&gt;📄 Adjustable Meeting Agenda.xlsx – Documentation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1detailed-description&#34;&gt;（1）Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This spreadsheet is a highly adjustable meeting agenda template designed for various team meetings. Users simply input the estimated duration for each agenda item, and the sheet automatically calculates start and end times, ensuring a well-structured and timely meeting. Pre-filled with typical meeting segments (e.g., introductions, agenda review, strategy discussion), it is fully customizable. Suitable for both in-person and virtual meetings, it helps facilitators manage time effectively and improve meeting productivity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Printable 2025 Monthly Calendar Template - Organize Your Year with Ease</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/any-year-calendar-1-month-per-tab/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/any-year-calendar-1-month-per-tab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;allowance-tracker-excel-template--documentation&#34;&gt;Allowance tracker Excel Template – Documentation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1detailed-description&#34;&gt;（1）Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This Excel calendar template is designed for 2025, featuring 12 separate monthly tabs with a Sunday-start layout. Each page includes clear date/weekday labels and a &amp;ldquo;NOTES&amp;rdquo; section for reminders. Its minimalist design is perfect for printing, ideal for personal scheduling, academic planning, or family organization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;2use-cases&#34;&gt;（2）Use Cases&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personal Use&lt;/strong&gt;: Track birthdays, medical appointments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;: Monitor exam schedules and study progress.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work&lt;/strong&gt;: Mark project deadlines and meetings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academic calendar with photos</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/academic-calendar-with-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/academic-calendar-with-photos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;file-structure&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;File Structure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1detailed-description&#34;&gt;（1）Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This “Academic Calendar with Photos” Excel template is a visually engaging and highly functional educational planning tool designed for students, teachers, school administrators, and homeschooling parents. It spans a full academic year from September 2025 to August 2026, organized by weeks and months with automatic day and date generation. The template includes dedicated note sections for key events such as parent-teacher conferences, exams, and holidays. Its clean layout supports photo insertion for personalization, making it ideal for academic scheduling, project tracking, and visual planning. Whether used in classrooms or at home, this template helps users manage their academic year efficiently and creatively.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple olive green timesheet invoice</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/templates/simple-olive-green-timesheet-invoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/templates/simple-olive-green-timesheet-invoice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;file-structure&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;File Structure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1detailed-description&#34;&gt;（1）Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &amp;ldquo;Simple Olive Green Timesheet Invoice&amp;rdquo; Excel template is designed for freelancers, consultants, and small businesses to efficiently track work hours and generate professional invoices. Featuring a clean olive-green layout, the template includes essential invoice details (invoice number, issue date, due date), service provider and client information sections, a time entry table, and automated calculations. Users simply input hours worked and rates, and the template automatically computes totals, subtotals, tax, and the final amount due. It supports up to 10 service entries, making it ideal for project-based work and service industries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
