<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Finance &amp; Accounting on ExcelNav</title>
    <link>https://excelnav.com/categories/finance--accounting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Finance &amp; Accounting on ExcelNav</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://excelnav.com/categories/finance--accounting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Free Balance Sheet Template - Track Assets &amp; Liabilities with Auto Calculations</title>
      <link>https://excelnav.com/templates/balance-sheet-simple/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://excelnav.com/templates/balance-sheet-simple/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-detailed-description&#34;&gt;1. Detailed Description&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This Balance Sheet Template is a powerful tool designed to help businesses and individuals track their financial health by automatically calculating total assets, liabilities, and owner&amp;rsquo;s equity. The template features organized sections for current/fixed/other assets, current/long-term liabilities, and equity investments. Formulas are pre-built to sum categories and validate the accounting equation (Assets = Liabilities + Owner&amp;rsquo;s Equity). A year-over-year comparison chart provides visual trend analysis, making it ideal for financial reporting, investor presentations, or loan applications. The template includes cell tips with instructions and supports accessibility features like alternative text for tables.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Baby Shower Planner Excel Template: Guest Lists, Budget &amp; Task Tracker</title>
      <link>https://excelnav.com/templates/basic-balance-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://excelnav.com/templates/basic-balance-sheet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-detailed-description&#34;&gt;（1）. ​Detailed Description​&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This Basic Balance Sheet Template is designed for Lamna Healthcare Company, providing a clear comparison of financial positions between 2024 and 2025. It includes three sections: ​Assets​ (current/fixed/other), ​Liabilities &amp;amp; Owner’s Equity​ (current/long-term/equity), and a yearly summary. Key metrics like cash, accounts receivable, investments, and payables are covered, ideal for analyzing liquidity, debt structure, and profitability. The template’s clean layout supports direct data input and instant calculations, making it a practical tool for accountants and entrepreneurs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academic club budget</title>
      <link>https://excelnav.com/templates/academic-club-budget/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://excelnav.com/templates/academic-club-budget/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;file-structure&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;File Structure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1detailed-description&#34;&gt;（1）Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Academic Club Budget is a financial management tool designed specifically for school academic clubs to track annual income and expenses effectively. It includes revenue sources such as membership dues, fundraisers, and donations, as well as common expenses like flyer printing and decorations. The sheet automatically calculates the budget for trips and the remaining amount needed, providing a clear overview of the club&amp;rsquo;s financial status. Ideal for middle schools, high schools, and universities, this template promotes financial transparency and efficient budget management for student-led organizations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activity costs tracker</title>
      <link>https://excelnav.com/templates/activity-costs-tracker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://excelnav.com/templates/activity-costs-tracker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;activity-costs-tracker--excel-template&#34;&gt;Activity Costs Tracker – Excel Template&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-detailed-description&#34;&gt;(1) Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Activity Costs Tracker is an Excel-based cost management tool designed for small and medium-sized businesses that need to accurately track cost structures across multiple product lines. Based on the Activity-Based Costing (ABC) methodology, this template categorizes expenses into direct costs, indirect costs, and general &amp;amp; administrative costs. It automatically calculates the cost per unit and total weekly production costs for each product. With a clear structure and pre-built formulas, users can generate detailed cost summaries effortlessly, enabling better financial control and informed decision-making. Ideal for managers, accountants, and business owners seeking a practical and efficient way to monitor product profitability.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annuity investment calculator</title>
      <link>https://excelnav.com/templates/annuity-investment-calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://excelnav.com/templates/annuity-investment-calculator/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;annuity-investment-calculator--excel-template&#34;&gt;Annuity Investment Calculator – Excel Template&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1detailed-description&#34;&gt;（1）Detailed Description&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Annuity Investment Calculator is a powerful Excel-based tool designed to simulate and track the growth of an annuity investment over time. Users can input the initial present value, annual interest rate, investment term, and monthly reinvestment rate to automatically calculate monthly interest earned, payout amounts, and updated balances. The template supports up to 20 years (240 months) of detailed monthly analysis and highlights key milestones such as the 7-year, 10-year, 14-year, and 20-year marks. Ideal for individual investors, financial advisors, and educational purposes, this tool helps visualize compound interest and long-term investment returns effectively.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
